

Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com www.LondonResearchInternational.com

Mr. Morgado

NATIONALITY: Portuguese

SUMMARY

As a Quantity Surveyor with extensive practical experience, I can utilise this knowledge to ensure successful completion of tasks. I have a genuine enthusiasm for construction and technology. I am also able to quickly establish as an efficient member of a team as well as able to work on own initiative.

EDUCATION

- Master in Municipal Engineering, Minho University Braga Portugal
 (MSc Dissertation: Evaluation of Positioning Accuracy of Low Cost GPS Equipments)
- BSc in Civil Construction Engineering (2nd cycle) Fernando Pessoa University – Porto – Portugal
- BSc in Civil Engineering (1st cycle) Instituto Superior de Engenharia do Porto – Portugal
- Land Surveyor Certification CICCOPN Maia Portugal

EMPLOYMENT RECORD/PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Quantity Surveyor: May 2013 – To date (Volunteer part-time)

People's Centre 4 Change, London – England

Team member in the development of a remodelling project to a Victorian building, to be the Centre's main office and adjoining services. Main responsibilities include:

- Estimating labour, material costs and forecasts to the different project alternatives;
- Preparing work schedules, plans, budgets and quantities;
- Dealing with technical issues and general inquiries on the progression of the project;
- Calculating costs and ensuring value for money during project deliver.



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com

www.LondonResearchInternational.com

Quantity Surveyor: February 2013 – April 2013 (freelance)

Tony Pestana Builders, London - England

Quantity surveying and cost estimating to house refurbishment works and extensions up to £200,000. Main responsibilities included:

- Prepare Supplier and Subcontractor enquiries, scrutinise quotations and undertake selection process;
- Produce bills of quantities, schedules of work and contractors proposal documents to support bids;
- Liaise with the Client and Suppliers to establish the project specification;
- Dealing with technical issues and general inquiries on the progression of the project;
- Calculating costs and ensuring value for money during project deliver;
- Comprehending and working to strict health and safety regulations.

Quantity Surveyor / Civil Engineer: October 2002 – December 2012 Construções José Gonçalves e Campos, Vila do Conde – Portugal

Building company specialized in new buildings and refurbishments: houses, offices and warehouses up to €10M. Main responsibilities included:

- Undertake the preparation and processing of quotations, bids and tenders;
- Prepare Supplier and Subcontractor enquiries, scrutinise quotations and undertake selection process;
- Produce bills of quantities, schedules of work and contractors proposal documents to support bids;
- Liaise with the Client, Subcontractors, Suppliers, and Operational Offices to establish the project specification;
- Dealing with technical issues and general inquiries on the progression of the project;
- Calculating costs and ensuring value for money during project deliver;
- Provide statistical reports to sites and weekly report analysis;
- Works supervision and planning;
- Project management;
- Setting out, levelling and monitoring;



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com www.LondonResearchInternational.com

- Site diary and record keeping;
- Building method statements;
- · Administrative work related to suppliers and clients;
- Registering invoices and ensure all costs are associated to a work order;
- Dealing with confidential personnel and payroll paper work.

Trainer: January 1998 – December 2010 (part-time)

CICCOPN, Maia – Portugal (www.ciccopn.pt)

Vocational training centre for building and public works industry of the north of Portugal

- Trainer of quantity/land surveying, works management amongst others;
- Assure meeting training requirements set by accrediting bodies;
- Managing the maintenance of training records and files;
- Maintaining and updating student handbooks, and producing training materials and handouts;
- Maintaining and developing course administration systems and procedures for the training programme run by CICCOPN;
- Representing and promoting CICCOPN to external relationships.

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS	
n/a	
PUBLICATIONS	
n/a	
LANGUAGES	

Portuguese, English